[{"question": "Choose facts about continue; statement is C Language.", "option1": "A) continue; is used to take the execution control to next iteration or sequence", "option2": "B) continue; statement causes the statements below it to skip for execution", "option3": "C) continue; is usually accompanied by IF statement.", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=14;\n    \n    while(a<20)\n    {\n        ++a;\n        if(a>=16 && a<=18)\n        {\n            continue;\n        }\n        printf(\"%d \", a);\n       \n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 15 16 17 18 19", "option2": "B) 15 18 19", "option3": "C) 15 16 20", "option4": "D) 15 19 20", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a correct statement about C break; statement.?", "option1": "A) break; statement can be\u00a0used inside switch block", "option2": "B) break; statement can be used with loops like for, while and do while.", "option3": "C) break; statement causes only the same or inner loop where break; is present to quit suddenly.", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a correct statement about C language break; statement.", "option1": "A) A single break; statement can force execution control to come out of only one loop.", "option2": "B) A single break; statement can force execution control to come out of a maximum of two\u00a0nested loops.", "option3": "C) A single break; statement can force execution control to come out of a maximum of three nested loops.", "option4": "D) None of the above.", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Choose a correct C Statement regarding for loop.\nfor(; ;);\n", "option1": "A) for loop works exactly first time", "option2": "B) for loop works infinite number of times", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=10, b, c;\n    b=a++;\n    c=++a;\n    printf(\"%d %d %d\", a, b, c);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 10 11 12", "option2": "B) 12 10 12", "option3": "C) 12 11 12", "option4": "D) 12 12 12", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0, b=0;\n    while(++a < 4)\n        printf(\"%d \", a);\n\n    while(b++ < 4)\n        printf(\"%d \", b);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 0 1 2 3 1 2 3 4", "option2": "B) 1 2 3 1 2 3 4", "option3": "C) 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4", "option4": "D) 1 2 3 4 0 1 2 3", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=10,b=20;\n    \n    if(a==9 AND b==20)\n    {\n        printf(\"Hurray..\");\n    }\n    \n    if(a==10 OR b==21)\n    {\n        printf(\"Theatre\");\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Theatre", "option2": "B) Hurray\nTheatre", "option3": "C) No output", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What are C ASCII character ranges.?", "option1": "A) A to Z = 65 to 91", "option2": "B) a to z = 97 to 122", "option3": "C) 0 to 9 = 48 to 57", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " Expand or Abbreviate ASCII with regard to C Language.", "option1": "A) Australian Standard Code for Information Interchange", "option2": "B) American Standard Code for Information Interchange", "option3": "C) American Symbolic Code for Information Interchange", "option4": "D) Australian Symbolic Code for Information Interchange", "ans": "B"}]
